

sadikk.ozel@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/sadikozel in



After successfully completing the optional preparatory class at the B2 level at the university, I graduated from Samsun Ondokuz Mayıs University, Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering in 2024. Since 2019, I have been interested in C / C +++ programming languages and have been developing various projects within the scope of the course and as a hobby. I share some of these projects on GitHub. The projects I have developed include a robot that can be controlled over Wi-Fi, a robot controlled by ESP32-CAM, addressable RGB LED, EMG amplifier, liquid level control, AC temperature control and food label analysis with OCR. I completed my compulsory internship in the R&D department of Simfer Global company and gained experience on various electronic components, cards and embedded software. I took part in the OMÜHENDİS Career Days team organized by the IEEE community of our university in 2020 and 2021 and volunteered at OKAF 2022, one of the regional career fairs. In addition, I took part in the software and hardware part of our Quadruped Robot team, which we established in the context of the Teknofest competition. Having a strong knowledge of hardware and software, I aim to advance my career in the field of software engineering and continue my studies in this direction.

### **Education**

Sadık ÖZEL

2018 - 2024

Electrical-Electronics Engineering / Ondokuz Mayıs University, Samsun

I completed the optional preparatory class at B2 level and my undergraduate education with a GPA of 3.39/4.

# **Experience**

JUL 2022 - SEP 2022

Intern / SiMFER, Kayseri

During my internship at Simfer in Kayseri from July 2022 to September 2022, I designed and developed circuit boards for electric and gas stoves. I gained experience in firmware development for microcontrollers and microprocessors used in electric and gas stoves. I also acquired knowledge in implementing communication protocols such as USB, SPI, I2C, and UART, and gained experience in power management of electric stoves. Additionally, I developed skills in using electronic tools such as oscilloscopes, spectrum analyzers, breadboards, electronic modules, and multimeters for testing and troubleshooting.

#### Skills

C/C++ • Python • ROS • SIEMENS TIA Portal • MATLAB • MS Office Applications

# **Projects**

#### Kasif Quadruped Robot

I collaborated with a team of four, taking on roles in 2D mapping, video transmission, and ground station sections to ensure the robot met desired specifications. The project was accepted for support by the TÜBİTAK-2209A project support program and reached the finals in the Teknofest 2023 competition in the "Technology for Humanity" category.

## References

Ali Furkan HASTÜRK - SİMFER - +90 505 955 97 40 Cengiz TEPE - Associate Professor at Ondokuz Mayıs University - +90 538 858 32 21